ALEXANDRIA BETH HARRIS

1106 Julia Ave | Louisville, KY 40204

(502) 724-8707 | xandi.harris@gmail.com | www.linkedin.com/in/xandiharris

Overview

Professional Ambitious business professional who has comprehensive understanding of employee relations, office administration, and web development. Adept at following complex instructions, helping to maintain company and federal policies. Specializes in customer service and administrative responsibilities including, but not limited to payroll processing, customer service, employee onboarding, project coordination, and professional development.

Education

Code Louisville/ JCTC; Louisville, KY Front End Web Development; July 2019 Full Stack Web Development; May 2020

Murray State University; Murray, KY

Bachelor of Science; May 2013

Major: Organizational Communication

Minor: Fine Arts

DuPont Manual Magnet High School; Louisville, KY

High School Diploma; May 2009

Professional Experience

TEKsystems; Louisville, KY

Administrative Assistant, May 2013-July 2013

Customer Support Associate, August 2013-April 2019

- Processed weekly payroll for over 200 technical professionals using PeopleSoft and sharepoint.
- Onboarded all technical professionals hired for state and local government positions within the local TEKsystems office.
- Maintained compliance records for all assigned consultants.
- Assisted in development and onboarding of team members including leading individualized and group training as new policies and procedures are launched.
- Responsible for running background investigation, drug testing, and I 9-verification for all new or rehired technical professionals.

Bath & Body Works; Louisville, KY

Sales Associate, May 2015- December 2015

- Maintained a high level of customer service to shoppers.
- Assisted in training of new sales associates.
- One of the top sellers each month during employment.

Baptist East Milestone Wellness Center; Louisville, KY

Locker Room Attendant, May 2010- August 2012

- Assisted members and visiting patrons in the locker room with various needs.
- Maintained friendly and clean atmosphere.

SAMs Club; Louisville, KY

Sales Associate, May 2012- August 2012

Kentuckiana Pool Management; Louisville, KY Pool Manager/ Lifeguard, May 2007- August 2011

The Forum at Brookside; Louisville, KY

Main Dining Area and Ambassador Dining Room Server, March 2007- June 2009

Key Skills

- Proficient with HTML, CSS, Javascript/JQuery, Microsoft Outlook, Word, Excel, PowerPoint, Access, Publisher, Facebook, Twitter, LinkedIn, Instagram, Sharepoint, Peoplesoft Systems, and WordPress.
- Experience with Adobe Illustrator, InDesign, and Photoshop.

Communication:

- Mastered skills in digital communication, team building, conflict negotiation, organizational leadership, organizational hierarchy, phone and email etiquette, managerial strategies, training and development, and persuasion techniques (sales).
- Confident with public speaking, developing and delivering presentations, and customer service.

Leadership

Lee Clark Residential College Council:

- Female Member at Large, 2009-2010
- President, 2010
- Wing Representative, 2011-2012

TEKsystems:

• Leader of the TEKsystems Field Support Midwest and Southeast Newsletters, 2015-2018

References

Professional References and Github account available upon request.